Let me explain with an example. Let me explain. Block is said to be
10 lakh customers and an event or in
that case the expenses could be incurred at one
time the customer will exercise the
option of IFA and for one time iTech has a
wonderful power of 10 lakh in 10 years. It all comes back again. All these are
in today's times. Some of these
features are in the slide. Before that
we
saw the PIN code and the location where the customer is
coming from the cost of care, the additive
coverage and this will pack into the AI ​​feature
and this is
[Music] We
said we want to make a very innovative
product so then we talked about three of four
features which are extremely innovative and we
spoke about that but one extremely important
element which we have brought
into this product is the artificial
intelligence thing we have a rich database we have
A rich understanding of the customers who have
but health insurance through us not only through
retail but also through group basis that we have said that let's
look at features which are extremely
close to this customer segment
so we have broken it down into many segments
based on age based on the family
size based on the pin code where the customer
is coming from what are the requirements how much does he
want to spend based on this we have a
past history we have tried to
map that against what the requirements could be
of this customer and given
artificial intelligence output the beauty
of this is that it is extremely close to what
a customer would ideally want so that's
Advance Plus in this product so we are
trying to make a package that will seem
extremely attractive to the customer from that it
is very difficult to tell an amount from where the premium starts
you might want to hear  It
probably starts from Rs 3,000 or Rs 4,000, but it is
not like that. So there is an entry age to the
product that you know can start from 21 or 25.
And if you look at the various pin
codes where the customer will want to come, then
probably the premium in Delhi will be different
from other cities.
But let me assure you that the pricing of the
product is extremely comparatively done. We have
mapped it with the
competing products and we have seen that the
pricing is very good. So if
any customer goes to buy or compares himself,
who has understanding, he will love
to see the pricing of this product. So we
have insured that there is
a five-year age bracket after which the
premium changes. So suppose let me give you an
example, I am 25 years old, right now
I enter to elevate till the age of 30. The
premium will remain the same. For example, when I turn 31,
that premium will change.  It will happen, so that is a
natural thing that happens in